这就是我们的关于ShareActionProvider的代码实现
Here's our coding solution for the share action
让我们从添加一个字符串来作为开始
provider. Lets start by adding a string. The
这个字符串会成为我们的行为的标签 现在我们要添加一个新的
string will be used for the label for our action. Now we're going to add a new
菜单资源  这些资源会被用于
menu resource. This resource will be for the
DetailFragment  我们将从添加名字域开始
detail fragment. We'll start by adding the name
这些名字域会被Android的支持库用到 在它的描述小部件的XML里
space used by the Android support library for
最后  我们添加这个我们实际需要的Item
it's widget XML. Finally, we add the actual item.
这个菜单项目包含我们从
This menu item contains the string that we
字符串文件里面添加的字符串
just added from the strings file. It's always
它总是作为一个Action被展示出来 所以它会出现在
shown as an action. So it appears on
操作栏中 它的actionProviderClass是Android支持库
the action bar. And its actionProviderClass is the ShareActionProvider
里面的ShareActionProvider。Android支持库
from the Android support library. The Android support
允许ShareActionProvider能被使用于比
library allows the ShareActionProvider to be used on earlier
Android 4.0之前的版本  4.0是它
versions of Android then 4.0. When it was
被官方添加到框架中时的Android版本。接下来，让我们进入
officially added to the framework. Next, let's go to
DetailAactivity  我们要看看
the DetailAactivity. We're going to be looking at the
DetailActivity中的DetailFragment。 所以我们能在这个Fragment里
DetailFragment within the DetailActivity. So the first thing
做的第一件事是添加一些有用的东西  让我们添加
we can do in our fragment is to add a few useful things. Let's add a log
一个记录标签，一个标记从哪分享的字符串，
tag, a string for the share hashtag, hashtag
#SunchineApp, 然后添加一个储存天气信息的字符串变量
sunshineApp, and we're going to take the forecast
作为这个类的成员。接下来
string and make it a member variable. Next
在onCreateView里，我们给天气变量赋予实际的值
in onCreateView, let's actually populate our member variable.
最后 用它来设置要显示的文本内容
And then finally, use it to set the text.
我们创建一个shareIntent。这个Intent使用ACTION_SEND
Lets create a shareIntent. This intent uses ACTION_SEND.
这个FLAG_ACTIVITY_CLEARED_WHEN_TASK_RESET是很重要的
This FLAG_ACTIVITY_CLEARED_WHEN_TASK_RESET is somewhat
设置了这个Flag，我们要分享去的Activity才
important. It prevents the activity we're sharing to from
不会被添加进Activity堆栈。
being place onto the activity stack. What will happen,
如果我们没有这个标志  接下来会发生的是
if we don't have this flag, is when you
一会儿当你点击返回键时
click on the icon to return to the application
你可能实际上会留在那个处理这个shareIntent的APP里
later, you may actually end up in another application.
而无法回到我们自己的APP。
The one that's actually handling the share intent. When
当你使用FLAG_ACTIVITY_CLEAR_WHEN_TASK_RESET时，它会真正返回你
FLAG_ACTIVITY_CLEAR_WHEN_TASK_RESET is used, it'll actually return you to your
的当前应用。我们设置Intent类型为“test/plain”
application instead. We've set the type, test/plain, to let
以让系统知道我们即将分享的是纯粹的文本
Android know we're going to be sharing plain text. And
然后添加我们要分享的天气信息字符串和我们的井号标签
then we share our forecast string plus our hashtag.
最后只剩下一件事要做了。我们
Only one more thing left to do. We have
要把这个菜单添加到这个Fragment里
to add the menu to the fragment. To do
为此，我们必须要设置一个Flag，它标示这个Fragment
this, we have to set a flag that this fragment
有一个选项菜单。否则，
has an options menu at all. Otherwise, it
它不会调用onCreateOpitionsMenu这个成员函数
won't actually call the onCreate options menu member
最后  这就是我们的onCreateOpitionsMenu成员函数
function. Finally, here's our on creat options member
正如你所见的  我们扩充了
function. As you can see, we're inflating the
我们早前创建的detailfragment菜单
detailfragment menu that we created earlier. Finding the
找到“分享”选项，拿到ShareActionProvider，然后链接我们的
share item, getting the ShareActionProvider, and attaching our
Intent到这个ShareActionProvider。无论什么时候你
intent to this ShareActionProvider. You'll want to update
要分享的数据改变了  它都会及时更新
this whenever the data you want to share changes.
这就是全部内容了  你现在添加了一个ShareActionProvider到Sunshine里
And that's it. You've now added a ShareActionProvider into Sunshine.